据我们所知
To our knowledge,
附近没有居民表现出类似的特征
no other nearby residents have exhibited similar traits.
那我们是怎么知道他的
So how did we find out about him?
有线人看见他在街头表演中
Informant saw him lighting torches in a street show...
用小手指点燃火把
with his pinkie.
由此引来了神盾局的关注
Brought it to S.H.I.E.L.D.'s attention.
我们叫他不能随便运用此能力
We told him to keep his abilities under wraps.
从那时起  他就列入目录上了
He's been on the index ever since.
什么目录
The index?
是神盾局保存超能力者与
It's a list S.H.I.E.L.D. keeps of people
富含能量物体的名单
and objects with powers.
等等  名单上有多少人啊
Wait. What? How many are there?
你是说更多的人有...
Are you saying there are more people --
没有很多
Not many.
都足够列个名单出来了....
Well, enough to keep a list.
一份很短的名单  是打算要保护他们
A short list, meant to protect them.
尽管某些少见的情况下神盾局会采取行动
Though, in rare cases, S.H.I.E.L.D. has had to take action.
采取行动对付物体还是人
Action against objects or people?